Are you a friend of Frendo?
Clown in a Cornfield is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Eli Craig.
Quinn and her father have just moved to the quiet town of
Kettle Springs hoping for a fresh start.
Instead, she discovers a fractured community that has fallen on hard times
after the treasured Baypen Corn Syrup Factory burned down.
As the locals bicker amongst themselves and tensions boil over, a sinister, grinning figure emerges
from the cornfields to cleanse the town of its burdens, one bloody victim at a time.
Quinn Maybrook, played by Katie Douglas.
Cole Hill, played by Carson MacCormac.
Mayor Arthur Hill, played by Kevin Durand.
Tyler Anderson, played by Dylan McEwan.
Dr. Glenn Maybrook, played by Aaron Abrams.
Matt, played by Alexandre Martin Deakin.
Clown in a Cornfield is a 2025 American slasher film directed by
Eli Craig and written by Craig and Carter Blanchard.
It is based on the 2020 novel of the same name by Adam Cesare, and stars Katie
Douglas, Aaron Abrams, Carson MacCormac, Kevin Durand, and Will Sasso.
Clown in a Cornfield premiered at South by Southwest on March 10, 2025,
followed by a theatrical release in the United States on May 9, 2025.
The film received average reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of small town, based on novel
or book, beheading, dark comedy, rifle.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.